http://www.vegsource.com/privacy.html

VegSource.com Privacy Policy
VegSource Interactive (Vegsource) is a website and newsletter service currently made available free of charge. We believe in the Golden Rule of treating visitors and subscribers as we would like to be treated, which means we don't spy on you. We believe we are in compliance with Europe's new privacy law, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Vegsource does access the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors to the website but no user login is required to access the website.
Visitors are welcomed to comment on blog posts and are asked for their first name (which can be an alias) and email address in order to do so but this data is not accessed or repurposed by the publisher.
Newsletter Email
Subscribers to the free newsletter are likewise asked for a first name and email address, in order for the newsletters to be correctly delivered by email.
The percentage of email- and page-opens are also tracked with great interest by us, the publisher, to better understand the interests of our readers so that I may give you what you want.
Advertising
Vegsource does sometimes run ads but does not directly collect data in order to advertise to you. Third-party advertiser networks used by Vegsource employ industry standard data collection that should be in compliance with the GDPR.
Information Disclosure
Vegsource has never and will never sell your information.
Data Storage
Vegsource uses third-party vendors and hosting partners for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology needed to run the website.
Third-Party Embeds
The video content that you see displayed on Vegsource is generally hosted by YouTube or sometimes Vimeo. These files send data to the hosted site just as if you were visiting that site directly (for example, when you load a post page from Vegsource with a YouTube video embedded in it, YouTube receives data about your activity). We do not control what data third parties collect or what they will do with it. Videos are covered by the privacy policy of the third-party service.
Tracking & Cookies
We do not use browser cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you return to our site and Vegsource doesn't track you across the Internet - it can't.
Some third-party services that we use, such as Google Analytics may place their own cookies in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by Vegsource only and not the use of cookies by third parties.
Data Security
We use encryption (HTTPS) to protect data transmitted to and from our site. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, so we can't guarantee security. You browse the Internet and Vegsource at your own risk, and you're responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your device.
Changes to this Policy
Vegsource may periodically update this Policy. We'll notify you about significant changes to it.
Questions
We welcome feedback about this policy at: support@vegsource.com
Categories of Recipients
Vegsource shares minimal anonymous data with third-party processors in order to provide the services. These processors offer at least the same level of data protection as that set out in this statement. This includes the following categories of recipients:
• Hosting, Storage, & Other Infrasructure
• Security
• Analytics
• Communication & Support
• Payment Processors
Search engines will index public interactions, and any user-generated content. Users may also share links to your content on social media.
Potential Consequences of Processing
By posting public comments on Vegsource, users may make certain personal data about themselves public and accessible to others. This may in some cases constitute special category protected data which is considered manifestly made public by the user.
Due to the public nature of information posted to Vegsource, it may be possible for third parties to derive identifying personal data from posts, whether by reading, inference, supplemental research, or automated extraction and analysis.
If you do not agree with and accept the risks of using the Internet and Vegsource, you may choose not to use the services.
Retention
Vegsource retains the minimal data associated with a newsletter subscription for the lifetime of your account. You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in the footer of this and every newsletter. This will ban that address from being resubscribed.
If you want to have your data completely removed and forgotten, please send an email from the address associated with your subscription with "FORGET ME" in all caps in the subject line to news@vegsource.com
If you wish to have public comments deleted, send a request to support@vegsource.com
To delete payment or billing information shared with a third party payment processor, you will need to do so with your payment provider.
Contact Information
VegSource Interactive c/o Mostly Magic Inc. 20555 Devonshire St. #105 Chatsworth, CA 91311 USA support@vegsource.com
If you don't accept our terms, please do not visit Vegsource.
Most Popular Articles This Month
Healthy Expo -- Oct 11-14 in Los Angeles!
867 views
China Study author Colin Campbell slaps down critic
625 views
Very cool: Food Revolution Summit April 27 -- And it's...
578 views
The Truth About the Weston Price Foundation
548 views
HOPE: What You Eat Matters (Full 2018 Documentary)
Copyright ©2020 VegSource Interactive, Inc. Reproduction of material from any VegSource pages without written permission is strictly prohibited.
VEGSOURCE ® is registered in the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office as a trademark of Mostly Magic, Inc.
